GEGEJOSPER CENIZA

WEB DEVELOPER / LARAVEL DEVELOPER



CONTACT ME AT

- San Jose, Aurora,Zamboanga del Sur,Philippines, 7020
- gegejosper@gmail.com
- +63917-7222-631
- in https://www.linkedin.com/i
 n/gegejosperceniza/

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Wordpress
- Laravel
- PHP
- MySQL
- LAMP
- Javascript
- CRM

SOFTWARE

- VS Code
- Sequel Pro
- CyberDuck
- Git
- Sourcetree

RECENT PROJECTS

- http://jujiedso.com
- http://skinaura.ph
- http://vative.com.au

PERSONAL PROFILE

A Web Developer since 2010 with experience in various tasks. A tech savvy and problem solver that you can rely on. Enthusiastic individual with superior skills in Wordpress and Laravel, Love to learn new technologies that will help me to grow in the industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

fFreelance Laravel Developer

AZWAYPH | Jan 2018 - Oct 2022

• Develop web application using Laravel that focuses on Finance, Logistics, E-Commerce, Subscriptions and Membership.

Wordpress Developer

BOSS DESIGNS | Sep 2020 - Oct 2022

- Develop Wordpress plugin
- Setup sales funnels
- Develop sites using wordpress

Senior Wordpress Developer

PyjamaBosses LLC | March 2016 - Jun 2018

- Setup sales funnel using infusonsoft and clickfunnels
- Develop Wordpress Sites
- Develop wordpress plugins

IT Head

LGU Aurora | July 2019 - July 2022

- Monitor the systems of the institution
- Develop web application using Laravel
- Computer Maintenance

EDUCATION HISTORY

WESTERN MINDANAO STATE UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, 2010

- Programmer of the Year
- Best Thesis of the Year